cppcryptfs - Copyright (C) 2016-2026 Bailey Brown. All rights reserved.
project url: github.com/bailey27/cppcryptfs
cppcryptfs is a user-mode cryptographic virtual overlay filesystem
cppcryptfs is based on the design of gocryptfs (github.com/rfjakob/gocryptfs)
cppcryptfs links with and incorporates source code from several open source projects.
All incorporated sources use the MIT license or other permissive open source licenses.
All statically linked libraries use a permissive open source license.

Some libraries which are linked with dynamically use the GNU LGPL.

cppcryptfs itself uses an MIT license which is as follows:

The MIT License (MIT)

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.