cppcryptfs usage: modified and incorporated into cppcryptfs (as SecureEdit.cpp and SecureEdit.h).
Secure Edit copyright and license: 
100% free Secure Edit control MFC class
Copyright (c) 2003 Dominik Reichl
If you use this class I would be more than happy if you mention my name somewhere in your application. Thanks!
Do you have any questions or want to tell me that you are using my class, e-mail me: <dominik.reichl@t-online.de>.