project url: github.com/arktronic/aes-siv
cppcryptfs usage: code from this project was modified and incorporated into cppcryptfs (in the cppcryptfs/aes-siv directory).
The low-level, third-party AES implementation included with aes-siv was replaced with a new implementation that uses OpenSSL.
aes-siv copyright and license:
This project is licensed under the OSI-approved ISC License:

Copyright (c) 2015 ARKconcepts / Sasha Kotlyar

Permission to use, copy, modify, and/or distribute this software for any purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.